If the brake is found to be contaminated with oil, proceed according to the instructions in the following video.
如果發現煞車被油污染，請按照以下影片中的指示進行。
Please note that this video is a general process and is not component specific.
請注意，這段影片是一般流程，並非針對特定零件。
If oil or grease was identified on the brake drum, brake shoes and in the rear nearby, position the car on top landing and lower the counterweight fully on the counterweight buffers.
如果在煞車鼓、煞車片和附近後方發現油或油脂，將車廂停在頂層，並將對重完全放在對重緩衝器上。
Inform your service leader that oil contamination has been identified and should be considered high risk.
通知你的服務主管，告知已發現油污染，應視為高風險。
Remove all remaining machine covers and prepare to inspect and clean the entire area Arrange brake shoes for replacement.
移除所有剩餘的機器蓋，準備檢查和清潔整個區域，安排更換煞車片。
Clean the machine and all surrounding areas with lint free cloths and VOC free non oil based cleaner.
用無絨布和不含揮發性有機化合物的非油基清潔劑清潔機器和周圍區域。
Check the grease quality at the outlet pipes and grease collectors Hard grease will require the outlet pipes to be cleaned.
檢查出口管和油脂收集器的油脂質量，硬油脂需要清潔出口管。
Remove the collectors and if possible the outlet pipes.
移除收集器，如果可能的話，移除出口管。
Clean all outlet pipes as good as possible and make sure that they are not blocked by old and hard grease.
盡可能清潔所有出口管，確保它們沒有被舊的硬油脂堵塞。
Before putting back the outlet pipe, check the outlet itself and remove hard grease.
在重新安裝出口管之前，檢查出口本身並移除硬油脂。
Reinstall the outlet pipe, clean the grease box and put it back Perform the same work on all other outlet and outlet pipes.
重新安裝出口管，清潔油脂箱並放回原位，對所有其他出口和出口管進行相同的工作。
If an automatic lubrication system is fitted to the machine, ensure the functionality and grease pipe connections are according field information 903.
如果機器裝有自動潤滑系統，確保其功能和油脂管連接符合903號現場信息。
The ALS should be switched off until the grease leakage has been identified and fixed.
在找到並修復油脂洩漏之前，應關閉自動潤滑系統。
Move the car up and take it off the buffers Pay attention to the brake performance after releasing the direction button The elevator should stop immediately.
將車廂移上並從緩衝器上移開，注意在釋放方向按鈕後的煞車性能，電梯應立即停止。
After the breakthrough replacement, conduct a brake capacity test and also a brake performance test Empty car up.
在更換煞車片後，進行煞車容量測試和煞車性能測試，空車上行。
Both these tests must be successful before the elevator could be put back into operation.
這兩項測試必須成功，電梯才能重新投入運行。
The brake capacity test might not be available on all the units Please contact your supervisor if you are not sure.
煞車容量測試可能並非所有單位都可用，如果不確定，請聯繫你的主管。
After the brake performance test, most of the controllers will provide you a deceleration rate.
在煞車性能測試後，大多數控制器會提供減速率。
Depends to the controller generation This information will be shown straight after the test or be stored in the controller sub menu.
根據控制器的代數，這些信息會在測試後立即顯示或存儲在控制器子菜單中。
For later reference, record the new values in the control cabinet or logbook For gearless machines and deceleration rates available, use the following table.
為了以後參考，將新數值記錄在控制櫃或日誌中，對於無齒輪機和可用的減速率，請使用以下表格。
For gearless machines without deceleration rate available, the following table can be used.
對於無齒輪機且無可用減速率，請使用以下表格。
More test variants and further information can be found in J42500101.
更多測試變體和進一步信息可在J42500101中找到。